The upstarts of the great
pirate era have gained a
momentum that not even the world
government is prepared for.
During this exciting age,
there's one man standing at the
epicenter of everyone's attention.
Monkey D.
Luffy and his crew, the Straw Hats.
In order to stay ahead of these
turbulent times, Every four years,
50 global leaders hold a World
Summit in the Holy Land of Marijua.
This event, known as the
Reverie, is about to begin.
The fate of the world is about
to take a dramatic new turn.
This is the current Navy headquarters,
led by the newly promoted fleet
Admiral Sakazuki, new Marine Ford.
Two years ago, in the War of the Best,
Navy forces battled against
the Whitebeard Pirates.
The skirmish ended in the Navy's victory.
However, the destruction to Marine
Ford was quite catastrophic.
The original base functioned as the
heart of the world's justice system.
But in order to acclimate
to the raging pirate era,
the world government constructed
an even greater fortress.
New Marine Ford has become
the new home of justice,
located at the entrance to the new world.
Fuji Dorry dared to show
his face in Marie Joie?
Yes, I'm afraid so, sir.
He was only to step foot in
a base under one condition.
By bringing me the heads
of Straw Hat and Law.
I thought I was extremely clear with
what I told him back in Dressrosa.
What's his excuse?
Wow, scary.
How dare he come back here
like nothing happened?
What a jackass. I'm sorry.
I'm afraid I don't have
any answers for you, sir.
Then tell me why didn't
you boot his ass, huh?
Well, he was armed with theoretical
rhetoric and we were powerless, sir.
If you ask me, it's fair game,
since this isn't military ground.
That yokel is just splitting hairs!
Take him with a grain of salt next time!
It's a tough job, huh?
Fleet Admiral?
Sengoku!
You stay out of this, you
semi-retired has-been!
So tell me, who else do
we have at Marie Joie?
Admiral Ryokugyu, sir!
Ryokugyu, huh?
Then contact him immediately! Yes, sir!
Even though the position of
Navy Headquarters has changed,
new Marine Forge still
serves the same purpose.
guarding the gates of Marie Joie
where the Celestial Dragons reside.
The location of the previous
base where the War of the
Best took place has become
the home of the G1 branch.
The two bases are
situated on either side of
the Red Line to protect
Marijois from attack.
This place is known as Red Port.
Like the Navy bases, each side of the
Red Line also has its own massive harbor.
The government has a novel means of crossing
the war that always draws attention.
Gondola one.
Now depart.
Look, Dad!
It's going up!
Bondolas, bubble-based gondolas,
make their way up to the holy
land of Brichois every day.
They're here!
Just look at all those ships pouring in!
Clear the way!
The royals are coming through!
It's Fear the Sixth of
the Rashwan Kingdom!
And he brought the Patricuses!
How cute!
Queen Moralone of the Tunzim Kingdom!
She's so beautiful!
Here's a toast to all the
lovely eyes in the world.
It's better to die standing
than live on your knees.
King Taco from the Kingdom of the Dead!
Look, King Hamburger of the
Bollywood Kingdom just showed up!
Is there a reason why
he's walking so slow?
Although my pace may be measured,
I vow I will never turn back!
A Navy ship?
Whoa, he made it!
It's the great knight of
the sea, King Neptune!
And look!
The three princes are with him, too!
The Ryukyu Kingdom's finally
here for the reverie! Yeah!
Let's boogaboshi!
Mambo on the water!
Mambo on the land!
I'm bringing the party wherever I stand!
I feel so free! Drum!
Are you two ready for this?
I was born ready!
Damn!
Thought I was gonna drown down there!
Hey, Miss Princess, come on out!
We can do this, Shirahoshi.
Together, let's go to Marie Joie.
Yes!
It's beautiful!
We couldn't wait to see you, Princess!
It has been 200 years
since the Ryugu Kingdom
began its affiliation
with the world government.
But in all that time, they've
attended the reverie only once before.
So this is indeed a rare occasion.
I wouldn't blame you if you had mixed
feelings about our little plan, Koala.
With the fishmen, I mean.
Must be tough.
They make it to the Reverie,
and then we invade it.
It's fine.
And besides,
the Reverie isn't what we have a problem
with, or even the world government.
It's just the Celestial Dragons.
They're our enemy.
Welcome!
We're all so excited to have you here!
She's so big and beautiful.
Hey, just like a dream!
Hey boss, she deserves
a feature story, right?
Princess Shirahoshi Is he gonna be okay?
Forget it, he can't even hear
us We love you, Princess!
Carp, I'm worried.
She seems to be a bit too popular.
Folks have been looking
forward to this for days.
Rumors were spreading saying your daughter
was as beautiful as the Pirate Empress.
She's gonna be a Bone Fight
celebrity, I'm afraid.
She is awfully pretty,
not to mention huge!
So everyone gets a good look!
Um, Mr.
Luffy's grandpa, sir?
That thing over there, what's it called?
Would it happen to be a forest?
No, that's just a tree.
Well, it's the great hero, Garth.
And you must know who
I am, needless to say.
Yeah, you're some stupid brat.
Now out of my way!
What was that?
I must have heard wrong.
He isn't joking, is he?
Unless he isn't isn't joking, that is.
How dare you.
I'm Stella, king of the Goa
kingdom from whence you hail.
You know what that means.
As one of my subjects, you answer to me.
I'll let you off this time, but you would
do well to remember that in the future.
Stella was taken in by Sabo's
parents, who are nobles.
With that as a foothold,
he and his new family
schemed to improve his
standing and wed him to
Princess Isntoinette.
Later, the king and the prince of the
Goa kingdom both mysteriously died.
And as a result, several months
ago, Stella rose to power.
Didn't expect those two to meet up!
Goa is a simple and quiet place, but
it's home to a fair number of outlaws.
Garp's the exception here.
It was home to the leader
of the Revolutionary Army.
They're second-in-command, too.
Roger's son, Ace.
And Straw Hat.
There's something
special about that place.
Now, if you'd like to apologize
by kneeling at my feet, please do.
Piss off, brat.
I got places to be.
The audacity of this man confounds me.
Let me cut to the chase, Garp.
I need connections, my good man.
Hold some strings so I can
become a celestial dragon.
They're all scumbags, you know.
What?
I hope nobody heard that.
I'll be put to death at this rate.
Wait.
Not supposed to say that.
I take it back.
He's terrifying.
There you are, young man.
Are you all right?
That thing can move?
I thought that was a statue.
Is he a giant?
I heard they eat humans and can
melt rocks with their saliva.
No, wait.
What are these things?
Fangs? Scales?
Look at the colors of their skin.
They must be fishmen.
More fish than man for certain.
They are under sea abominations.
Beasts who spread disease
to humans by mere contact.
Don't touch me!
Bandola 2 now deported.
So long.
You folks take it easy. Thank you, Mr.
Luffy's grandpa, sir.
It was fun traveling with you.
I can't wait to see more
of the surface world.
We're so high.
It's like a dream.
Is something the matter, dear daughter?
The sun!
I can hardly believe it!
Look, brothers!
The sun is so radiant I can
feel its warmth! Indeed.
The sky reaches up and up forever!
And the endless sea stretches
out across the horizon,
sparkling in the sunlight
like dancing jewels.
Gotta admit, it makes me wanna mumble!
I never knew that such a beautiful
world was waiting for us.
It's like I'm seeing the
light for the first time.
I must admit, the sun tree on the
ocean floor pales in comparison.
This is where I want to be, Father.
If I can, I wish to stay
here on the surface.
And I want to show this
dazzling world bathed in
light to all the people
of our kingdom as well.
I'll ask them—that's what the
reverie is all about, after all!
all
Got it.
For the record, Sakazuki told
me to find you and kick you out.
Do you want to fight?
Yeah, no thank you.
I think I'll pass on that.
Besides, it's not like you're going
to destroy the conference, right?
Not at all, but there is
something I do want to destroy.
The system.
That aside, thanks for the meal.
It was fine indeed.
You traveled a long way to get here.
How is old man Vegapunk doing?
Well,
not that I could see it, of course, but
he's got quite a creation on his hands.
You wanna give me a clue?
We won't need the seven
warlords, not anymore!
Off your rocker, as usual!
I love it!
I'll say it once more.
The food here is truly excellent.
I noticed you haven't had a single bite.
Am I to assume that?
But you're still on your fast.
If I went, ah, and a fine woman
put some food in, I'd eat.
But that's not happening.
So I haven't eaten a thing
in three years or so.
Help!
Stop the wind!
It's scary!
Simmer down, lad
Did you see that?
I don't know what you're
referring to A giant!
He was in the wall, just staring at us
with some kind of trident and a dumb hat.
You must be hallucinating?
Why would a face be lurking in a mountain?
I know what I saw!
Why are there so many
crows and they're huge?
It's rare to see them up this high.
So these must be birds. How cute.
They really can't fly.
If they peck at the bubble,
they'll fall and die. Go away.
Kaido, come here.
Do your job.
Shoot down these crows.
This is a clear safety hazard.
Don't worry, Kinstein. You'll be fine.
Just you wait and see.
Riding a Bondola, they travel high up
to Marijoire at the top of the Red Line.
I hope you had a pleasant trip.
Please watch your step.
Merfolk!
The atmospheric pressure is different here,
so please use these reinforced bubbles.
Why, thank you!
It's huge!
From here,
the guests ascend along an
extravagant staircase leading
to a land that lies at the
center of all four seas.
It is the largest continent in the
world and rests at the highest altitude.
We're almost there, King Steady!
The descendants of those who created
the world itself reside here.
And the name of this beautiful place,
the Holy Land of Mariejoie.
Oh, I want to live here.
Fruit, please!
It's such a lovely place.
Is that green spot
there a forest, perhaps?
It's man-made, but yes.
So this is it, Mariejoie.
Hmm, looks like it's still
quite a trek to the castle.
Please, come this way.
Take these handles and
hold on, if you would.
An earthquake!
The ground's moving on its own!
Help!
Someone protect me!
This is called a travelator.
The pathway will carry you.
Father, perhaps we should
follow this side path.
Shit Hachi, you wanted to look
at the forest, didn't you?
Fukaboshi.
Isn't the scenery beautiful here?
Better for us to take our time.
I think that's a wonderful idea.
Father, you don't mind if
we stroll for a bit, do you?
It would be my pleasure.
We shall escort you.
Those stupid fish.
Afraid of modern technology,
bunch of savages,
I simply must procure one
of these for my kingdom.
The travelator, you say?
Travelator, actually—call
it what you like!
I
don't know why, but
something feels wrong here?
Not
too fast, not too slow—make it nice and
easy, keep the pace steady, you fools!
you fools
If you stop, then you get the whip!
Someone save me, or at least kill me!
Father, Lock, Lock!
What's wrong, Charlos?
It's a mermaid, and she's big, too!
Open the gate!
It would appear that all the royal families
have brought their bodyguards with them.
They aren't armed, but they
look rather formidable.
They have quite the feast laid out for us.
It'll be nothing but conferences
for seven days starting tomorrow.
So the leaders better
have fun while they can.
Though I suppose the other
guests just get to party.
I'm the king of Samba, and
in my land, Samba's king.
Would you like to dance with me, Samba?
King Samba?
But I can't Mambo!
Samba! Mambo!
Shake it! Shake it!
Seems father is getting
along well with everyone.
That's good.
Can I help you?
So the rumors are true.
You are breathtakingly beautiful, my dear.
Might I introduce you to my son?
He's single, you know. Wow.
She's not bad, Papaw. Not bad.
Princess!
Princess, my handsome son here is a
prince and you might be a good match.
Papa, I like the big lady a lot.
If you're looking for a prince, then
surely you can't do better than my boy.
I have three handsome princes who
would love to have a chat with you.
Princess, which one do you like best?
No one.
I'm sorry, but...
David, you're my type! Why not?
They're princes, aren't they?
Ow!
Damn it!
How dare you humiliate me!
No, she was saying I'm not married
either in an under-Z dialect.
This is all a misunderstanding.
She was merely using
a moral colloquialism.
When this happens, just say something like,
how lovely, but I can't possibly choose.
Gotta let them down softly, okay?
But if I told them that,
then I would be lying.
It's not lying, it's redirecting.
Better than starting a
diplomatic emergency.
Now let's go.
So let's eat it.
How cute.
You're like a little fairy.
I could just eat you up.
I'm a warrior, I'll have you know.
so that is not a compliment!
You okay there, Leo?
I didn't mean anything by it.
Sorry I insulted you. Huh?
Well, then that's okay.
He's safe.
She is nice, after all.
You certainly can move fast.
I didn't notice at all
until Karoo spotted you.
I allowed myself to be seen because I heard
that you were friends with Luffy Land.
We are the Straw Hat
subordinates, you know.
And we're pirates, too.
Little pirates?
That's so cute!
And it's a pleasure to meet you.
A pleasure to meet you as well!
This is such a nice surprise.
I wasn't expecting to meet so many
of Lucy's friends at the reverie.
But then again, the Straw Hats are
traveling the world, I suppose.
Did Lucy visit your country as well?
Or Luffy, I mean?
Yeah!
Tell us!
He did.
In fact, if it wasn't for them, The kingdom
of Alabasta wouldn't even exist today.
Princess Vivi from Alabasta, a desert
kingdom located on the Grand Line.
She encountered the Straw
Hats more than two years ago
and traveled on the ship as
a close friend for some time.
Crocodile, who was a warlord
of the sea at the time,
looked to take control of Alabasta.
As a result,
the kingdom was locked in civil war
between the royal army and rebel forces.
Crocodile's plot was thwarted
by Luffy and friends.
At last, the Alabasta
Kingdom was saved. However,
the world government reported the Navy was
responsible to hide the fact
that pirates won the day.
They don't like to be seen as heroes.
Their bounties keep
getting higher and higher.
The whole world probably
knows about them now.
Still, they haven't changed
one bit, my friends.
When I read about what
happened in Dressrosa, I knew.
They saw someone in need,
so I'll bet they did everything in
their power to save them, right?
Yeah, he did!
Luffy did more than just save me.
He saved our kingdom.
The Straw Hats are the
heroes of all Dressrosa!
I miss you, Lucy.
Excuse me?
Um, were the two of you talking about Mr.
Luffy just now?
The Mermaid Princess!
Shirahoshi!
Talking about him doesn't
mean they know him.
Luffy's still a pirate, after all.
You mustn't let people
know he's your friend.
Hmm, the Mermaid Princess knows Luffy?
Wait, you were asking if
we're friends with Luffy?
Hold on, Rebecca.
You shouldn't say too much.
Yes, I was right!
So you were talking about him! Stop it!
Maybe they were saying how bad he is!
I owe a great debt of gratitude to Luffy.
Us too!
Oh, speaking of Luffy, he
sure eats a lot, doesn't he?
Yeah, if he's not eating, he's
probably thinking about it.
He certainly enjoys a
good feast, doesn't he?
Seems they're having fun.
That they are.
I would say this bodes well
for the future of our nations.
We've made good friends in no time at all.
Though I admit, it's a strange connection.
Indeed, royal families united by
the goodwill of the Straw Hats.
Excuse me, aren't you
Rebecca from Dressrosa?
Wow, look who it is!
It's me, Sai!
Funny, feels like the last time I
ran into you was just the other day!
And have you been well?
Better than ever!
It seems he is from Kano's Hapasue army.
I heard that the old warrior Qin
Zhao stepped down not too long ago.
He did.
That man's the new leader.
Hi, Aisa!
Hey, brother!
I didn't think I'd see you here, too, Leo.
I'm the secret bodyguard.
What a reliable ally. Agreed.
Is he a friend of yours?
Yeah, and we exchanged cups
of sake with Lufilun together.
Hey, Leo.
Listen, I'm doing my part in working
hard for the kingdom of Kano.
But after this bodyguard job
is done, I'm cutting ties.
When I make a vow, I
don't take it lightly.
I owe a great debt to the Straw Hats.
After they saved me,
and I intend to pay it back all seven
representatives of the
Straw Hat fleet along with
all five thousand six hundred of our troops
have to be ready to aid him at any time!
Hmm, I heard the other members
have started preparing as well?
What is this?
You think you can resign
from the Standing Kingdom?
Just like that!
Tell me why!
Forgive me, but there's
a debt I must repay.
Barrier!
Barrier crush!
Stay behind the barrier and
cross your fingers for good luck.
That's my battle-tested
secret for success.
We surrender!
Please, just show us mercy.
We'll even serve under you.
Whatever you want.
Good.
Then put this on.
What is it?
Wear this and show your support
for the Straw Hats with us. Do it!
Two unidentified ships
are approaching, sir.
Here to avenge Doflamingo.
What Cavendish?
Oh, it's nothing like that.
I was the prince of the bourgeois
kingdom, as you may already know.
Naturally, all the women in the
kingdom were absolutely crazy about me.
They refused to marry any
man other than myself,
and so I was expelled from the kingdom,
charged with the crime of being too popular.
Uh, so in other words, the ships pursuing
us are not enemies, but my adoring fans.
I know there's people even
stronger than Doflamingo out there,
and I'm sure that Straw Hat will
face many of them in combat.
If we want to help, we must build
our own strength, too. Agreed.
My crew and I are training hard every day,
and I hope we can fight
together by Luffy Lund's side.
Right!
Well, if it isn't Princess Phoebe!
Wapol!
You fool!
What's a goon like you doing here?
A fine question.
I have Straw Hat to thank.
He sent me flying away to a strange
and distant land, but I'm back, baby!
And in charge!
So, you fools.
Want to know how my darling
rose to power again?
What a coincidence!
They must be friends of
Luffy's as well! Not quite.
He's an enemy.
That old funny Daddy
King Cobra doing well?
Actually, I know he's not doing well.
I saw him earlier.
I was making a joke at your expense.
You, darling, you're the best!
I rarely call Dick your hero!
You're the funniest man in the universe!
Gush, gush, gush!
Huh?
That's enough of your jokes.
It's sickening that you
came to power again.
I feel sorry for whatever
country you rule.
Yee-hee-hee!
The world government should be ashamed.
They've got no standards
if they let you back in.
Dalton!
And that witch!
How are you still alive?
Asking about my beauty regimen?
Not a chance!
Dalton! Dr. Kureha!
So nice to see you again!
Hello, Vivi.
You're looking more regal than ever.
Are you happy?
If I'd known you were a princess back then,
I would have stuck you in a higher bill.
That's for darn sure.
Who are these two?
They're friends from a
snow-covered island that
I traveled to with Luffy
and the other Straw Hats.
While we were on our way to
Alabasta, Nami suddenly fell ill.
We needed to find a doctor.
So we stopped on the
nearest inhabited island.
Dalton helped Luffy get rid of Wapol and
became a bit of a hero to the kingdom.
So he was appointed as king,
and the Drum Kingdom was reborn
as the Cherry Blossom Kingdom.
That's lovely.
Hey, hey, hey!
You're getting a real big head.
Perhaps I need to remind you,
you're still my subordinate.
Those days have long since passed.
Now.
I've become a king.
I won't bow to you.
Wow, Dalton.
You're acting like royalty already.
You are a natural.
Uh, come on.
Nah!
Listen up, Dalton!
You useless goody-two-shoes!
If you wanna make it as a ruler,
you gotta get your hands dirty!
I clawed my way back to the top,
making a fortune with my munch-munch
powers, and trust me, I know!
The higher up you climb,
the sooner you'll see!
This whole world is corrupt!
That tip was free, but the next
one will cost you your life!
Oh, and by the way, did you
read the article on Luffy?
Yes, from top to bottom.
Oh, I get it.
You're like us. Huh?
Lucy's fan.
Be honest, you like Luffy Lynn, don't ya?
He's the best.
I thought so.
The underwater prison, impel down.
The bottom floor level six holds the most
dangerous criminals the
world has ever known.
It's called the infinite hell.
Putting me in solitary, are you?
I'm so lonely, why Magellan?
Or is this a plot to protect me? Maybe?
Is there an assassin from
on high out to kill me?
Of course I'd better
watch my loose tongue.
What a rotten mess I could cause!
Just think—what if I told the whole
world the secret Maurice was hiding? Why?
why Why does it matter
if it's revealed now?
Power doesn't last long.
It'll rot faster than anyone thinks.
I don't know.